dislikelike.com 2012-05-24

# Privacy Policy | DislikeLike.Com

The following Privacy Policy summarizes the various ways that the [www.disikelike.com](http://www.dislikelike.com/) ("Service Provider", "we" or "our") treats the information you provide while using [www.disikelike.com](http://www.dislikelike.com/) ("Website"). It is our goal to bring you information about our services, at the same time, protect your privacy. 

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. Your use of and/or registration on any aspect of the Website will constitute your agreement to this Privacy Policy. If you cannot agree with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website. This Privacy Policy does not cover information collected elsewhere, including without limitation offline and on sites linked to from the Website. In addition to reviewing this Privacy Policy, please read our Terms and Conditions page. Your use of the Website constitutes agreement to its conditions as well. This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time; the date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page, so check back often. Continued access of the Website by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy.

**1\. THE TYPE OF INFORMATION THE WEBSITE COLLECTS**

The Website generally collects personally identifying information with your specific knowledge and consent. For instance, when you register for any portion of our services, you are asked to provide information such as your e-mail address, name or phone number. Optional information such as your age or gender may also be requested. Our servers may also automatically collect information about your computer when you visit the Website, including without limitation the type of browser software you use, the operating system you are running, the website that referred you, and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. Your IP address is usually associated with the place from which you enter the Internet, like your Internet Service Provider, your company or your university.

**2\. HOW THE WEBSITE USES INFORMATION PROVIDED BY YOU**

Service Provider uses personally identifying information you supply through the Website to provide you with the service you have requested. We may also use the information to communicate with you about new features, products or services, and/or to improve the services that we offer by tailoring them to your needs. In addition, we reserve the right to use the information we collect about your computer, which may at times be able to identify you, for any lawful business purpose, including without limitation to help diagnose problems with our servers, to gather broad demographic information, and to otherwise administer our Website.

**3\. COOKIES**

You may have read about "cookies," nuggets of information that are placed by a Website in a storage place on your own computer. We may use cookies to track usage patterns on the site, to deliver content, and to record registration and personalization of information. For example, if you register on any part of the Website and are given the option to save your user name and password on your computer, we can provide this convenience to you by placing a cookie on your computer. Our cookies may contain personally identifiable information but we will not share this information with any other companies. If you don't want any cookies, your Web browser likely includes an option that allows you to not accept them. However, if you set your browser to refuse cookies, some portions of the Website may not function properly.  
**  
4\. INFORMATION SECURITY AND NOTIFICATION**

Because no data transmission over the Internet is completely secure, and no system of physical or electronic security is impenetrable, Service Provider can not guarantee the security of the information you send to us or the security of our servers or databases, and by using the Website you agree to assume all risk in connection with the information sent to us or collected by us when you use the Website. In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you. If notification is appropriate, we may notify you by e-mail (provided we have your e-mail address).

If you have any concerns or questions about any aspect of this policy, please feel free to contact us (add **info** ) **@dislikelike.com**.
